{
  "id": "da-de-mix-pack-02",
  "name": "Dänisch ↔ Deutsch – Mix Pack 02 (500)",
  "src": "DA/DE",
  "tgt": "DE/DA",
  "cards": [
    {
      "front": "erbse",
      "back": "ært"
    },
    {
      "front": "lyn",
      "back": "blitz"
    },
    {
      "front": "erdbeere",
      "back": "jordbær"
    },
    {
      "front": "gardin",
      "back": "vorhang"
    },
    {
      "front": "bjerg",
      "back": "berg"
    },
    {
      "front": "hospital",
      "back": "krankenhaus"
    },
    {
      "front": "was",
      "back": "hvad"
    },
    {
      "front": "chokolade",
      "back": "schokolade"
    },
    {
      "front": "sytten",
      "back": "siebzehn"
    },
    {
      "front": "medicin",
      "back": "medikament"
    },
    {
      "front": "sol",
      "back": "sonne"
    },
    {
      "front": "schmutzig",
      "back": "beskidt"
    },
    {
      "front": "træ",
      "back": "baum"
    },
    {
      "front": "juli",
      "back": "juli"
    },
    {
      "front": "flugzeug",
      "back": "fly"
    },
    {
      "front": "klaver",
      "back": "klavier"
    },
    {
      "front": "küche",
      "back": "køkken"
    },
    {
      "front": "apfel",
      "back": "æble"
    },
    {
      "front": "müssen",
      "back": "skulle"
    },
    {
      "front": "wollen",
      "back": "ville"
    },
    {
      "front": "socken",
      "back": "strømper"
    },
    {
      "front": "tafel",
      "back": "tavle"
    },
    {
      "front": "löffel",
      "back": "ske"
    },
    {
      "front": "zucker",
      "back": "sukker"
    },
    {
      "front": "tiger",
      "back": "tiger"
    },
    {
      "front": "ryg",
      "back": "rücken"
    },
    {
      "front": "film",
      "back": "film"
    },
    {
      "front": "gehen",
      "back": "gå"
    },
    {
      "front": "stein",
      "back": "sten"
    },
    {
      "front": "wissenschaftler",
      "back": "forsker"
    },
    {
      "front": "pære",
      "back": "birne"
    },
    {
      "front": "krankheit",
      "back": "sygdom"
    },
    {
      "front": "ulv",
      "back": "wolf"
    },
    {
      "front": "rezept",
      "back": "recept"
    },
    {
      "front": "bauch",
      "back": "mave"
    },
    {
      "front": "schuh",
      "back": "sko"
    },
    {
      "front": "otte",
      "back": "acht"
    },
    {
      "front": "hass",
      "back": "had"
    },
    {
      "front": "hemd",
      "back": "skjorte"
    },
    {
      "front": "bauer",
      "back": "landmand"
    },
    {
      "front": "zwiebel",
      "back": "løg"
    },
    {
      "front": "aprikose",
      "back": "abrikos"
    },
    {
      "front": "baumwolle",
      "back": "bomuld"
    },
    {
      "front": "reservierung",
      "back": "reservation"
    },
    {
      "front": "kaffe",
      "back": "kaffee"
    },
    {
      "front": "krawatte",
      "back": "slips"
    },
    {
      "front": "kellner",
      "back": "tjener"
    },
    {
      "front": "ohren",
      "back": "ører"
    },
    {
      "front": "fire",
      "back": "vier"
    },
    {
      "front": "værelse",
      "back": "zimmer"
    },
    {
      "front": "november",
      "back": "november"
    },
    {
      "front": "tordenvejr",
      "back": "gewit­ter"
    },
    {
      "front": "fodbold",
      "back": "fußball"
    },
    {
      "front": "haus",
      "back": "hus"
    },
    {
      "front": "angst",
      "back": "angst"
    },
    {
      "front": "teller",
      "back": "tallerken"
    },
    {
      "front": "holz",
      "back": "træ"
    },
    {
      "front": "supermarkt",
      "back": "supermarked"
    },
    {
      "front": "zug",
      "back": "tog"
    },
    {
      "front": "komme",
      "back": "kommen"
    },
    {
      "front": "tochter",
      "back": "datter"
    },
    {
      "front": "unten",
      "back": "nede"
    },
    {
      "front": "receptionist",
      "back": "rezeptionist"
    },
    {
      "front": "laufen",
      "back": "løb"
    },
    {
      "front": "enden",
      "back": "slutte"
    },
    {
      "front": "schnell",
      "back": "hurtig"
    },
    {
      "front": "laut",
      "back": "høj"
    },
    {
      "front": "fødder",
      "back": "füße"
    },
    {
      "front": "drikke",
      "back": "trinken"
    },
    {
      "front": "kort",
      "back": "karte"
    },
    {
      "front": "frisør",
      "back": "friseur"
    },
    {
      "front": "juni",
      "back": "juni"
    },
    {
      "front": "cousine",
      "back": "kusine"
    },
    {
      "front": "hval",
      "back": "wal"
    },
    {
      "front": "ankomsttid",
      "back": "ankunftszeit"
    },
    {
      "front": "vej",
      "back": "straße"
    },
    {
      "front": "langsom",
      "back": "langsam"
    },
    {
      "front": "vorhersage",
      "back": "vejrudsigten"
    },
    {
      "front": "opgave",
      "back": "aufgabe"
    },
    {
      "front": "zitrone",
      "back": "citron"
    },
    {
      "front": "schwester",
      "back": "søster"
    },
    {
      "front": "bandage",
      "back": "verband"
    },
    {
      "front": "handske",
      "back": "handschuh"
    },
    {
      "front": "ingeniør",
      "back": "ingenieur"
    },
    {
      "front": "stuhl",
      "back": "stol"
    },
    {
      "front": "gras",
      "back": "græs"
    },
    {
      "front": "taxa",
      "back": "taxi"
    },
    {
      "front": "ziege",
      "back": "ged"
    },
    {
      "front": "spiel",
      "back": "spil"
    },
    {
      "front": "sprechen",
      "back": "tale"
    },
    {
      "front": "ost",
      "back": "käse"
    },
    {
      "front": "læder",
      "back": "leder"
    },
    {
      "front": "bil",
      "back": "auto"
    },
    {
      "front": "stolz",
      "back": "stolthed"
    },
    {
      "front": "sort",
      "back": "schwarz"
    },
    {
      "front": "grim",
      "back": "hässlich"
    },
    {
      "front": "skærm",
      "back": "bildschirm"
    },
    {
      "front": "oktober",
      "back": "oktober"
    },
    {
      "front": "journalist",
      "back": "journalist"
    },
    {
      "front": "flod",
      "back": "fluss"
    },
    {
      "front": "zahn",
      "back": "tand"
    },
    {
      "front": "kniv",
      "back": "messer"
    },
    {
      "front": "zwölf",
      "back": "tolv"
    },
    {
      "front": "e-mail",
      "back": "email"
    },
    {
      "front": "es",
      "back": "det"
    },
    {
      "front": "bäckerei",
      "back": "bager"
    },
    {
      "front": "sofa",
      "back": "sofa"
    },
    {
      "front": "bagved",
      "back": "hinten"
    },
    {
      "front": "mobil",
      "back": "handy"
    },
    {
      "front": "gæster",
      "back": "gäste"
    },
    {
      "front": "kunne",
      "back": "können"
    },
    {
      "front": "vind",
      "back": "wind"
    },
    {
      "front": "plaster",
      "back": "pflaster"
    },
    {
      "front": "umschlag",
      "back": "kuvert"
    },
    {
      "front": "beginnen",
      "back": "begynde"
    },
    {
      "front": "schön",
      "back": "smuk"
    },
    {
      "front": "wasser",
      "back": "vand"
    },
    {
      "front": "zehn",
      "back": "ti"
    },
    {
      "front": "bog",
      "back": "buch"
    },
    {
      "front": "temperatur",
      "back": "temperatur"
    },
    {
      "front": "nudeln",
      "back": "pasta"
    },
    {
      "front": "warm",
      "back": "varm"
    },
    {
      "front": "tanzen",
      "back": "dans"
    },
    {
      "front": "vierzehn",
      "back": "fjorten"
    },
    {
      "front": "skrive",
      "back": "schreiben"
    },
    {
      "front": "nebel",
      "back": "tåge"
    },
    {
      "front": "reisepass",
      "back": "pas"
    },
    {
      "front": "ankomst",
      "back": "ankunft"
    },
    {
      "front": "ananas",
      "back": "ananas"
    },
    {
      "front": "frosch",
      "back": "frø"
    },
    {
      "front": "salt",
      "back": "salz"
    },
    {
      "front": "onsdag",
      "back": "mittwoch"
    },
    {
      "front": "træt",
      "back": "müde"
    },
    {
      "front": "hvidløg",
      "back": "knoblauch"
    },
    {
      "front": "stoppested",
      "back": "haltestelle"
    },
    {
      "front": "finden",
      "back": "finde"
    },
    {
      "front": "åbne",
      "back": "öffnen"
    },
    {
      "front": "udenfor",
      "back": "außen"
    },
    {
      "front": "fahrrad",
      "back": "cykel"
    },
    {
      "front": "hjælpe",
      "back": "helfen"
    },
    {
      "front": "os",
      "back": "uns"
    },
    {
      "front": "freude",
      "back": "glæde"
    },
    {
      "front": "augen",
      "back": "øjne"
    },
    {
      "front": "krankenschwester",
      "back": "sygeplejerske"
    },
    {
      "front": "druer",
      "back": "trauben"
    },
    {
      "front": "auge",
      "back": "øje"
    },
    {
      "front": "seine",
      "back": "hans"
    },
    {
      "front": "wie",
      "back": "hvordan"
    },
    {
      "front": "huhn",
      "back": "høne"
    },
    {
      "front": "foto",
      "back": "foto"
    },
    {
      "front": "einfach",
      "back": "nem"
    },
    {
      "front": "viskelæder",
      "back": "radiergummi"
    },
    {
      "front": "gangplads",
      "back": "gangplatz"
    },
    {
      "front": "lautsprecher",
      "back": "højttaler"
    },
    {
      "front": "leise",
      "back": "lav"
    },
    {
      "front": "euch",
      "back": "jer"
    },
    {
      "front": "telefon",
      "back": "telefon"
    },
    {
      "front": "kort",
      "back": "karten"
    },
    {
      "front": "ameise",
      "back": "myre"
    },
    {
      "front": "politibetjent",
      "back": "polizist"
    },
    {
      "front": "fleisch",
      "back": "kød"
    },
    {
      "front": "blomst",
      "back": "blume"
    },
    {
      "front": "højre",
      "back": "rechts"
    },
    {
      "front": "vorn",
      "back": "foran"
    },
    {
      "front": "bleistift",
      "back": "blyant"
    },
    {
      "front": "gammel",
      "back": "alt"
    },
    {
      "front": "kartoffeln",
      "back": "kartofler"
    },
    {
      "front": "tablet",
      "back": "tablet"
    },
    {
      "front": "du",
      "back": "du"
    },
    {
      "front": "kopfhörer",
      "back": "hovedtelefoner"
    },
    {
      "front": "bjørn",
      "back": "bär"
    },
    {
      "front": "bager",
      "back": "bäcker"
    },
    {
      "front": "suchen",
      "back": "lede"
    },
    {
      "front": "hvilken",
      "back": "welcher"
    },
    {
      "front": "weil",
      "back": "fordi"
    },
    {
      "front": "eller",
      "back": "oder"
    },
    {
      "front": "mein",
      "back": "min"
    },
    {
      "front": "gris",
      "back": "schwein"
    },
    {
      "front": "smerte",
      "back": "schmerz"
    },
    {
      "front": "tage",
      "back": "nehmen"
    },
    {
      "front": "hud",
      "back": "haut"
    },
    {
      "front": "spiegel",
      "back": "spejl"
    },
    {
      "front": "programmierer",
      "back": "programmør"
    },
    {
      "front": "han",
      "back": "er"
    },
    {
      "front": "rød",
      "back": "rot"
    },
    {
      "front": "får",
      "back": "schaf"
    },
    {
      "front": "fünf",
      "back": "fem"
    },
    {
      "front": "hende",
      "back": "sie (akk.)"
    },
    {
      "front": "svær",
      "back": "schwierig"
    },
    {
      "front": "großmutter",
      "back": "bedstemor"
    },
    {
      "front": "neunzehn",
      "back": "nitten"
    },
    {
      "front": "apotek",
      "back": "apotheke"
    },
    {
      "front": "universitet",
      "back": "universität"
    },
    {
      "front": "elf",
      "back": "elleve"
    },
    {
      "front": "fisch",
      "back": "fisk"
    },
    {
      "front": "tennis",
      "back": "tennis"
    },
    {
      "front": "musiker",
      "back": "musiker"
    },
    {
      "front": "billig",
      "back": "billig"
    },
    {
      "front": "pilz",
      "back": "svamp"
    },
    {
      "front": "hungrig",
      "back": "sulten"
    },
    {
      "front": "wohnung",
      "back": "lejlighed"
    },
    {
      "front": "torv",
      "back": "platz"
    },
    {
      "front": "unser",
      "back": "vores"
    },
    {
      "front": "brev",
      "back": "brief"
    },
    {
      "front": "stjerne",
      "back": "stern"
    },
    {
      "front": "jacke",
      "back": "jakke"
    },
    {
      "front": "heiß",
      "back": "varm"
    },
    {
      "front": "far",
      "back": "vater"
    },
    {
      "front": "mappe",
      "back": "mappe"
    },
    {
      "front": "mütze",
      "back": "hue"
    },
    {
      "front": "kirsebær",
      "back": "kirsche"
    },
    {
      "front": "restaurant",
      "back": "restaurant"
    },
    {
      "front": "strand",
      "back": "strand"
    },
    {
      "front": "pilot",
      "back": "pilot"
    },
    {
      "front": "børn",
      "back": "kinder"
    },
    {
      "front": "haben",
      "back": "have"
    },
    {
      "front": "ko",
      "back": "kuh"
    },
    {
      "front": "werden",
      "back": "blive"
    },
    {
      "front": "flugticket",
      "back": "flybillet"
    },
    {
      "front": "ordner",
      "back": "ringbind"
    },
    {
      "front": "god",
      "back": "gut"
    },
    {
      "front": "museum",
      "back": "museum"
    },
    {
      "front": "arbeiten",
      "back": "arbejde"
    },
    {
      "front": "lørdag",
      "back": "samstag"
    },
    {
      "front": "schmetterling",
      "back": "sommerfugl"
    },
    {
      "front": "torsdag",
      "back": "donnerstag"
    },
    {
      "front": "lukke",
      "back": "schließen"
    },
    {
      "front": "lied",
      "back": "sang"
    },
    {
      "front": "hals",
      "back": "hals"
    },
    {
      "front": "kopf",
      "back": "hoved"
    },
    {
      "front": "schiff",
      "back": "skib"
    },
    {
      "front": "zwanzig",
      "back": "tyve"
    },
    {
      "front": "hvilke",
      "back": "welche (pl.)"
    },
    {
      "front": "feuerwehrmann",
      "back": "brandmand"
    },
    {
      "front": "brød",
      "back": "brot"
    },
    {
      "front": "pause",
      "back": "pause"
    },
    {
      "front": "mund",
      "back": "mund"
    },
    {
      "front": "kissen",
      "back": "pude"
    },
    {
      "front": "onkel",
      "back": "onkel"
    },
    {
      "front": "dreizehn",
      "back": "tretten"
    },
    {
      "front": "trauer",
      "back": "sorg"
    },
    {
      "front": "büro",
      "back": "kontor"
    },
    {
      "front": "links",
      "back": "venstre"
    },
    {
      "front": "nøgle",
      "back": "schlüssel"
    },
    {
      "front": "blå",
      "back": "blau"
    },
    {
      "front": "nase",
      "back": "næse"
    },
    {
      "front": "sohn",
      "back": "søn"
    },
    {
      "front": "nær",
      "back": "nahe"
    },
    {
      "front": "bærbar",
      "back": "laptop"
    },
    {
      "front": "lave",
      "back": "machen"
    },
    {
      "front": "affe",
      "back": "abe"
    },
    {
      "front": "sein",
      "back": "være"
    },
    {
      "front": "tee",
      "back": "te"
    },
    {
      "front": "zimmerkarte",
      "back": "nøglekort"
    },
    {
      "front": "essen",
      "back": "spise"
    },
    {
      "front": "banan",
      "back": "banane"
    },
    {
      "front": "fahren",
      "back": "køre"
    },
    {
      "front": "wer",
      "back": "hvem"
    },
    {
      "front": "dreieck",
      "back": "trekant"
    },
    {
      "front": "null",
      "back": "nul"
    },
    {
      "front": "seemann",
      "back": "sømand"
    },
    {
      "front": "ticket",
      "back": "billet"
    },
    {
      "front": "køreplan",
      "back": "fahrplan"
    },
    {
      "front": "læge",
      "back": "arzt"
    },
    {
      "front": "freundlich",
      "back": "venlig"
    },
    {
      "front": "forældre",
      "back": "eltern"
    },
    {
      "front": "grün",
      "back": "grøn"
    },
    {
      "front": "juice",
      "back": "saft"
    },
    {
      "front": "bi",
      "back": "biene"
    },
    {
      "front": "krokodille",
      "back": "krokodil"
    },
    {
      "front": "studerende",
      "back": "student"
    },
    {
      "front": "lernen",
      "back": "lære"
    },
    {
      "front": "sie (pl.)",
      "back": "de"
    },
    {
      "front": "montag",
      "back": "mandag"
    },
    {
      "front": "læse",
      "back": "lesen"
    },
    {
      "front": "skov",
      "back": "wald"
    },
    {
      "front": "bohne",
      "back": "bønne"
    },
    {
      "front": "dårlig",
      "back": "schlecht"
    },
    {
      "front": "qualle",
      "back": "vandmand"
    },
    {
      "front": "menü",
      "back": "menu"
    },
    {
      "front": "kjole",
      "back": "kleid"
    },
    {
      "front": "bier",
      "back": "øl"
    },
    {
      "front": "himmel",
      "back": "himmel"
    },
    {
      "front": "ohr",
      "back": "øre"
    },
    {
      "front": "hoste",
      "back": "husten"
    },
    {
      "front": "pande",
      "back": "pfanne"
    },
    {
      "front": "kind",
      "back": "barn"
    },
    {
      "front": "verkäufer",
      "back": "sælger"
    },
    {
      "front": "aber",
      "back": "men"
    },
    {
      "front": "anzug",
      "back": "jakkesæt"
    },
    {
      "front": "give",
      "back": "geben"
    },
    {
      "front": "spinat",
      "back": "spinat"
    },
    {
      "front": "hendes",
      "back": "ihre"
    },
    {
      "front": "afgang",
      "back": "abfahrt"
    },
    {
      "front": "bror",
      "back": "bruder"
    },
    {
      "front": "dem",
      "back": "sie (obj.)"
    },
    {
      "front": "zwei",
      "back": "to"
    },
    {
      "front": "løve",
      "back": "löwe"
    },
    {
      "front": "maj",
      "back": "mai"
    },
    {
      "front": "limette",
      "back": "lime"
    },
    {
      "front": "bus",
      "back": "bus"
    },
    {
      "front": "sæde",
      "back": "sitzplatz"
    },
    {
      "front": "bild",
      "back": "billede"
    },
    {
      "front": "hvorfor",
      "back": "warum"
    },
    {
      "front": "café",
      "back": "café"
    },
    {
      "front": "drucker",
      "back": "printer"
    },
    {
      "front": "hund",
      "back": "hund"
    },
    {
      "front": "kaufen",
      "back": "købe"
    },
    {
      "front": "lampe",
      "back": "lampe"
    },
    {
      "front": "hat",
      "back": "hut"
    },
    {
      "front": "liebe",
      "back": "kærlighed"
    },
    {
      "front": "marts",
      "back": "märz"
    },
    {
      "front": "notesbog",
      "back": "notizbuch"
    },
    {
      "front": "wann",
      "back": "hvornår"
    },
    {
      "front": "papir",
      "back": "papier"
    },
    {
      "front": "mais",
      "back": "majs"
    },
    {
      "front": "ampel",
      "back": "trafiklys"
    },
    {
      "front": "klima",
      "back": "klima"
    },
    {
      "front": "nederdel",
      "back": "rock"
    },
    {
      "front": "lila",
      "back": "lilla"
    },
    {
      "front": "reis",
      "back": "ris"
    },
    {
      "front": "bett",
      "back": "seng"
    },
    {
      "front": "hvor",
      "back": "wo"
    },
    {
      "front": "bad",
      "back": "badeværelse"
    },
    {
      "front": "schauspieler",
      "back": "skuespiller"
    },
    {
      "front": "stift",
      "back": "pen"
    },
    {
      "front": "ihn",
      "back": "ham"
    },
    {
      "front": "hände",
      "back": "hænder"
    },
    {
      "front": "dig",
      "back": "dich"
    },
    {
      "front": "kryds",
      "back": "kreuzung"
    },
    {
      "front": "park",
      "back": "park"
    },
    {
      "front": "verspätung",
      "back": "forsinkelse"
    },
    {
      "front": "and",
      "back": "ente"
    },
    {
      "front": "fuß",
      "back": "fod"
    },
    {
      "front": "seks",
      "back": "sechs"
    },
    {
      "front": "skak",
      "back": "schach"
    },
    {
      "front": "fernseher",
      "back": "fjernsyn"
    },
    {
      "front": "tante",
      "back": "tante"
    },
    {
      "front": "dienstag",
      "back": "tirsdag"
    },
    {
      "front": "fugl",
      "back": "vogel"
    },
    {
      "front": "kartoffel",
      "back": "kartoffel"
    },
    {
      "front": "ni",
      "back": "neun"
    },
    {
      "front": "quadrat",
      "back": "kvadrat"
    },
    {
      "front": "togbillet",
      "back": "bahnticket"
    },
    {
      "front": "spørge",
      "back": "fragen"
    },
    {
      "front": "hotel",
      "back": "hotel"
    },
    {
      "front": "tasse",
      "back": "kop"
    },
    {
      "front": "syv",
      "back": "sieben"
    },
    {
      "front": "uld",
      "back": "wolle"
    },
    {
      "front": "pfirsich",
      "back": "fersken"
    },
    {
      "front": "dass",
      "back": "at"
    },
    {
      "front": "peber",
      "back": "pfeffer"
    },
    {
      "front": "regn",
      "back": "regen"
    },
    {
      "front": "afgangstid",
      "back": "abfahrtszeit"
    },
    {
      "front": "flughafen",
      "back": "lufthavn"
    },
    {
      "front": "svømning",
      "back": "schwimmen"
    },
    {
      "front": "spille",
      "back": "spielen"
    },
    {
      "front": "markierer",
      "back": "overstregningstusch"
    },
    {
      "front": "aftale",
      "back": "termin"
    },
    {
      "front": "booking",
      "back": "buchung"
    },
    {
      "front": "ny",
      "back": "neu"
    },
    {
      "front": "see",
      "back": "sø"
    },
    {
      "front": "hähnchen",
      "back": "kylling"
    },
    {
      "front": "saks",
      "back": "schere"
    },
    {
      "front": "butik",
      "back": "laden"
    },
    {
      "front": "rosa",
      "back": "lyserød"
    },
    {
      "front": "tisch",
      "back": "bord"
    },
    {
      "front": "chauffør",
      "back": "fahrer"
    },
    {
      "front": "socke",
      "back": "strømpe"
    },
    {
      "front": "dyr",
      "back": "teuer"
    },
    {
      "front": "gelb",
      "back": "gul"
    },
    {
      "front": "kunstner",
      "back": "künstler"
    },
    {
      "front": "haj",
      "back": "hai"
    },
    {
      "front": "ræv",
      "back": "fuchs"
    },
    {
      "front": "rejse",
      "back": "reise"
    },
    {
      "front": "gaffel",
      "back": "gabel"
    },
    {
      "front": "kreis",
      "back": "cirkel"
    },
    {
      "front": "oppe",
      "back": "oben"
    },
    {
      "front": "topf",
      "back": "gryde"
    },
    {
      "front": "bælte",
      "back": "gürtel"
    },
    {
      "front": "cousin",
      "back": "fætter"
    },
    {
      "front": "türkis",
      "back": "turkis"
    },
    {
      "front": "misundelse",
      "back": "neid"
    },
    {
      "front": "stoff",
      "back": "stof"
    },
    {
      "front": "mælk",
      "back": "milch"
    },
    {
      "front": "schnupfen",
      "back": "forkølelse"
    },
    {
      "front": "drikkepenge",
      "back": "trinkgeld"
    },
    {
      "front": "ren",
      "back": "sauber"
    },
    {
      "front": "hane",
      "back": "hahn"
    },
    {
      "front": "computer",
      "back": "computer"
    },
    {
      "front": "mig",
      "back": "mich"
    },
    {
      "front": "braun",
      "back": "brun"
    },
    {
      "front": "fredag",
      "back": "freitag"
    },
    {
      "front": "biograf",
      "back": "kino"
    },
    {
      "front": "schriftsteller",
      "back": "forfatter"
    },
    {
      "front": "frakke",
      "back": "mantel"
    },
    {
      "front": "brokkoli",
      "back": "broccoli"
    },
    {
      "front": "glas",
      "back": "glas"
    },
    {
      "front": "bahnhof",
      "back": "banegård"
    },
    {
      "front": "maus",
      "back": "mus"
    },
    {
      "front": "torden",
      "back": "donner"
    },
    {
      "front": "elefant",
      "back": "elefant"
    },
    {
      "front": "regning",
      "back": "rechnung"
    },
    {
      "front": "en",
      "back": "eins"
    },
    {
      "front": "vinduesplads",
      "back": "fensterplatz"
    },
    {
      "front": "mango",
      "back": "mango"
    },
    {
      "front": "ur",
      "back": "uhr"
    },
    {
      "front": "serviet",
      "back": "serviette"
    },
    {
      "front": "musik",
      "back": "musik"
    },
    {
      "front": "femten",
      "back": "fünfzehn"
    },
    {
      "front": "bukser",
      "back": "hose"
    },
    {
      "front": "skole",
      "back": "schule"
    },
    {
      "front": "sie",
      "back": "hun"
    },
    {
      "front": "klein",
      "back": "lille"
    },
    {
      "front": "dezember",
      "back": "december"
    },
    {
      "front": "arm",
      "back": "arm"
    },
    {
      "front": "august",
      "back": "august"
    },
    {
      "front": "koffer",
      "back": "kuffert"
    },
    {
      "front": "visum",
      "back": "visum"
    },
    {
      "front": "decke",
      "back": "tæppe"
    },
    {
      "front": "forstå",
      "back": "verstehen"
    },
    {
      "front": "fjern",
      "back": "weit"
    },
    {
      "front": "ben",
      "back": "bein"
    },
    {
      "front": "wandern",
      "back": "vandring"
    },
    {
      "front": "sehen",
      "back": "se"
    },
    {
      "front": "krabbe",
      "back": "krabbe"
    },
    {
      "front": "vrede",
      "back": "wut"
    },
    {
      "front": "cykling",
      "back": "radfahren"
    },
    {
      "front": "teppich",
      "back": "tæppe"
    },
    {
      "front": "wein",
      "back": "vin"
    },
    {
      "front": "reception",
      "back": "empfang"
    },
    {
      "front": "feber",
      "back": "fieber"
    },
    {
      "front": "ihr (poss.)",
      "back": "deres"
    },
    {
      "front": "bedstefar",
      "back": "großvater"
    },
    {
      "front": "sturm",
      "back": "storm"
    },
    {
      "front": "und",
      "back": "og"
    },
    {
      "front": "februar",
      "back": "februar"
    },
    {
      "front": "sne",
      "back": "schnee"
    },
    {
      "front": "kat",
      "back": "katze"
    },
    {
      "front": "mond",
      "back": "måne"
    },
    {
      "front": "arkitekt",
      "back": "architekt"
    },
    {
      "front": "stor",
      "back": "groß"
    },
    {
      "front": "wichtig",
      "back": "vigtig"
    },
    {
      "front": "tre",
      "back": "drei"
    },
    {
      "front": "theater",
      "back": "teater"
    },
    {
      "front": "skildpadde",
      "back": "schildkröte"
    },
    {
      "front": "ferien",
      "back": "ferie"
    },
    {
      "front": "lehrer",
      "back": "lærer"
    },
    {
      "front": "kleber",
      "back": "lim"
    },
    {
      "front": "seksten",
      "back": "sechzehn"
    },
    {
      "front": "internet",
      "back": "internet"
    },
    {
      "front": "meine",
      "back": "min"
    },
    {
      "front": "april",
      "back": "april"
    },
    {
      "front": "arztin",
      "back": "læge"
    },
    {
      "front": "sælge",
      "back": "verkaufen"
    },
    {
      "front": "delfin",
      "back": "delfin"
    },
    {
      "front": "januar",
      "back": "januar"
    },
    {
      "front": "innen",
      "back": "indenfor"
    },
    {
      "front": "paprika",
      "back": "peberfrugt"
    },
    {
      "front": "schlafen",
      "back": "sove"
    },
    {
      "front": "kalt",
      "back": "kold"
    },
    {
      "front": "tørstig",
      "back": "durstig"
    },
    {
      "front": "wir",
      "back": "vi"
    },
    {
      "front": "din",
      "back": "dein"
    },
    {
      "front": "blomkål",
      "back": "blumenkohl"
    },
    {
      "front": "arbeit",
      "back": "arbejde"
    },
    {
      "front": "tastatur",
      "back": "tastatur"
    },
    {
      "front": "eksamen",
      "back": "prüfung"
    },
    {
      "front": "mekaniker",
      "back": "mechaniker"
    },
    {
      "front": "pinguin",
      "back": "pingvin"
    },
    {
      "front": "schuhe",
      "back": "sko"
    },
    {
      "front": "kalender",
      "back": "kalender"
    },
    {
      "front": "tænder",
      "back": "zähne"
    },
    {
      "front": "ich",
      "back": "jeg"
    },
    {
      "front": "hæfte",
      "back": "heft"
    },
    {
      "front": "überraschung",
      "back": "overraskelse"
    },
    {
      "front": "gurke",
      "back": "agurk"
    },
    {
      "front": "schrank",
      "back": "skab"
    },
    {
      "front": "mor",
      "back": "mutter"
    },
    {
      "front": "eichhörnchen",
      "back": "egern"
    },
    {
      "front": "butter",
      "back": "smør"
    },
    {
      "front": "hjerte",
      "back": "herz"
    },
    {
      "front": "håndbold",
      "back": "handball"
    },
    {
      "front": "schüler",
      "back": "elev"
    },
    {
      "front": "lineal",
      "back": "lineal"
    },
    {
      "front": "grå",
      "back": "grau"
    },
    {
      "front": "hest",
      "back": "pferd"
    },
    {
      "front": "meer",
      "back": "hav"
    },
    {
      "front": "rektangel",
      "back": "rechteck"
    },
    {
      "front": "sonntag",
      "back": "søndag"
    },
    {
      "front": "orange",
      "back": "appelsin"
    },
    {
      "front": "gitarre",
      "back": "guitar"
    },
    {
      "front": "svare",
      "back": "antworten"
    },
    {
      "front": "salat",
      "back": "salat"
    },
    {
      "front": "euer",
      "back": "jeres"
    },
    {
      "front": "pflaume",
      "back": "blomme"
    },
    {
      "front": "sport",
      "back": "sport"
    },
    {
      "front": "hvid",
      "back": "weiß"
    },
    {
      "front": "ø",
      "back": "insel"
    },
    {
      "front": "scham",
      "back": "skam"
    }
  ]
}